HKT48 vs NGT48  SashiKita Furious Battle!!
Good Evening!
Good Evening! Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you
Such a big scene setting
but only two of us
Yes
It's quite lonely, isn't it?
Yes, it is
Actually, other members do not know that
we already started our programme
Ehh? really?
Yes!
It's because our first battle is
"Dokkiri" so no one knows about this!
This is such a wicked!
<The first battle is...
< to remember the names of the staffs
who they will first meet today!
<We held this Dokkiri for these two teams
<to evaluate their necessary skills in the show biz
or being entertainers
Let's see what is happening in the dressing room!
W ow! they look cheerful!
This is good, isn't it?
We told them that camera men
will go into their room to take behind the scene atmosphere
So don't worry! You will see everything in detail!
that is great
but they are too cheerful, aren't they?
yes
All right! The staff is going to meet them!
Good morning!
It's started!
It looks so real!
Mori-san can make everyone believe!
Good evening!
If it were me, I would also believe this.
I am the producer, Mori.
That AD looks strange.
Nice to meet you
Before we start recording
I would like to introduce our staffs
although some are still not here yet
yes
<The first staff is chief producer
Usui (bald head)
<and of course he is the faked staff
I am the chief producer
Usui, Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you too
ah! Natsumikan can't hold her laugh already. This is bad!
I have very high hope with this programme
However, please be safe.
or else you will  have bald head like me,
Usui (bald head).
Bald head, the same as my name, Usui.
my name may be Usui but
I really do not want to be bald head.
Nako and Miku is laughing too out loud
so cuteee
< then Usui gives his hand-made rice balls to everyone.
<Will these young idols eat those hand-made rice balls
given by their first-met uncle?
It will be not good if I give only this side so..
Lovetan got it already! What will she do with it?
She will never eat it!
trying to smell it like this is not good...Stop Stop Stop!!
That is a bad manner here
Ogiyuka looks displeased
Yes! NGT Team looks like they are disgusted
They look a little disgusted
may be it's because their pride in the rice
because they are from Niigata??
Yes, so they can't eat the rice from Tokyo anymore.
HKT starts having it!
Ah! Madoka also has it. I'm surprised!
Ah! Miku is so cute!
Everyone is having it
they looks happy having it
Delicious!
She also praised it!
but Lovetan is still not having it
<Next is an AD who is always fail, Shimada.
I am Shimada. I am an Assistant Director.
AKB48, everyone.....
No, they are not AKB...they are NGT and HGT!!!
Aren't they AKB?
Ah!
You didn't listen when they introduced themselves, didn't you?
Nice to meet you
Shimada!
Shimada!!
Kind-hearted! Katomina is so kind!
Sorry. Thank you.
I will try my best! Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you
It looks like everyone cheers him on instead
<Next staff is a handsome AP, Ichuin.
<What will they react to this handsome staff??
Excuse me
All HKT members are stunned for a second!!
It's like they were casted a spell on
I'd like to introduce myself a little. Please line up.
They look a little strange.
They response to him in very different way!
She smiles explicitly and looks so happy
I am this programme AP, Ichuin. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too!
As I am an AP so
I will always take care of everyone as much as possible
so please tell me if you need any help.
- Will it be ok!?
Yes, please do.
I am also an AP.
and I bought some macarons for everyone
look at every single of them reacting at him
It's totally different from earlier!
Yes, it really does
very different from when they got the rice balls
It's too different!
now they are all excited with it
I am surprised that Katomina likes handsome guy!
yes, I'm also surprised
I'm shocked!
I didn't think they will act totally different like this!
but look at Nako-chan! She's still having the riceballs!
Cute one!!
Still having the riceball
Everyone! Be ready! Staffs will be ready soon!
Please wait a little longer.
yes
Excuse me
Thank you
Ah! She did it again!
wait wait wait! last time Rika-chan didn't help, did she?
Rika-chan is interesting
that's second time
It's not!
but she didn't help Shimada-san earlier.
<Next! Two more staffs will come and greet them.
I am the Sound staff, Goroumaru.
My surname is the same as a Rugby player.
but we are not related
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you too
I am camera man, Nakamura.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too
<This faked camera man, Nakamura. He actually has a great influence on this programme.
<He actually is
because He is this TV channel producer!!
The genuine one
I am Nakamura. I am
the NTV station's producer
Nice to meet you
Nakamura-san. He is in a very high position.
but now he disguises as a camera man
- I see
So if you don't try to remember every staff names seriously and equally
You will never be able to memorize it surely
Yes, I agree
<After every staff has finished introducing themselves,
<Now is the time for our fake programme to start!
This programme will have these two teams fight each other!
but I am concerned about something
which is?
Our 1st class army is not here.
Eh! Isn't it rude?
Just take a look! I got Natsumikan here and that made the result cleared!
3th army is here already!! hahaha!
Katomina-chan!
- yes!
What do you think about your true first TV programme?
Yes... I feel very thankful.
to whom?
NTV? isn't it?
so you do thank to NTV.
Let's start our first battle!
Who got the most powerful arm?
Furious Arm-wrestle!
I am just kidding!
Eh!?
Today battle actually is
Which side can remember the staffs names more?!!!
Everyone! Take it easy!
Are you ok? Yamada-san
Yamada-san?
yes...
Your face is funny, Yamada-san.
No! My face is cute!
Cute face!!
Fight!
Charge!!
SashiKita furious battle!
First faked staff. Please come out.
Who is he?
Eh? Is he the faked one?
This staff told you that he was
the chief producer.
but actually he is an actor
who is not related with this programme at all.
Let's see if you guys still remember his name?
This is easy.
- Are you sure?
because of this area?
finished?
Please show your answer!
Everyone got the right answer...
but Nako....
Nako is the only one with the different answer
She may got it correct.
yes, she may be only one who got it.
so let him tell his name.
Excuse me, may I have your name please?
Chief Producer, Usui.
Only Nako got the wrong answer!
This one is not that difficult, isn't it?
yes, it's easy
Nako answer was "Usu". She got some parts, did't she?
yes, I can only remember that.
If you could start the word correctly, the others wouldn't be any problem.
yes, just remember "Usu" (bald). that should be enough.
He played a gag which was not funny at all. Remember?
I think the riceball taste
was worse than the gag
Was it that bad?
I think because your tongue is used to high quality rice.
Yes, because we are from Niigata.
which is the place for growing rice, isn't it?
and the next one is
What is his name?
He looks so real. It's difficult, isn't it?
yes, he is.
I wouldn't be surprised, if he were real.
Please show your answer
they are different?
Shimada-san , Shimada-san...
Santa-san?
I am sorry
Yamada-san's face is really funny, isn't it?
eh! look at the board! Not my face please!
She answered Santa-san
Looks like almost everyone answered Shimada-san
HKT
Shimada-san , Shimada-san , Yoshida-san, Toshio-san
Shimada-san , Shimada-san , Tano-san , Kobayashi-san
Please give us the answer! Your name is?
AD, Shimada.
So NGT got 4 correct answers
and... 1 2 3 4! It's equal!
It's a great battle!
Trying to read his name backward and you'll find out that...
Damashi (faked)
No clue, huh?
Damn!
When he got blamed, what did you think? Mio-chan.
I thought "can he make it?"
He also called us "AKB" which was totally wrong....
yes
Is he alright? this guy...
How about you Natsumikan? Being called "AKB"
I felt glad though.
Yes, this is AKB. hahaha.
The next one is..
Ahhhh! This one... This one...He's that handsome man back there!
Cool!
Everyone is just too excited!
I'm sorry but he also is our faked staff and
you will never see him in the programme again!
Ehhhh~~~
I can see your sadness on your faces! You guys are just too obvious!
Nooooooo
It changes nothing!!
By the way, I was surprised with Katomina's action back there.
To overly offer her help to him!
but I think there is someone who shocked me more than her!
It's Rika-chan!!!
Rika-chan!
Rika-chan, Do you know that how you react
between riceball and macaron is totally different!
I didn't have riceball but macaron
did you? that's not good!
Let's see the answer.Show you answer!
NGT
Ikarashi-san, Ichuin-san..
What?? I can't read it.
Ijimei-san
and Ikemen or Nitto (wool hat)
Macaron-san
Oh! Katomina named him in such a international way!"Junk"
What's on your mind?
I just look at his face and...
His face it too handsome, isn't it?
yes
All right! how about HKT?
Kiryuin-san
such a waste..Who is Kiryuin-san?
Ichuin-san
Sakurasaka-san
Takeo-san
Kobayashi-san
Saito-san
Ichuin-san
Ryuonchi-san
eh..but I got the feeling
do you?
It's too weird
The feeling is right, I guess.
Yes, but I don't think it the correct answer.
Let him tell his name
Your name, please.
Assistant Producer, Ichuin.
So each team got 2 correct answers
then 2 points for both team
What's on you mind when you see their answers?
well, Tada-san...
Ota-san!
Sorry, Ota-san
What!!! I can remember yours but you can't remember mine!!!
Don't mess it up! Ichuin!!!
I thought my charm got Ota-san
Really?
But actually I like the man who
is plain, not handsome.
So you are not my type!
Especially Natsumikan
Well, actually I....... By the way,
you are just a common guy?
I am a model
I see
Indeed! I can tell from his face!
"I can tell from his face"??
Who are you??? How can you dare saying something like that?
And the real AP is there.
Hanasuga-san.
Hanasuga-san
I guess everyone is thinking that
this kind of face is really the real AP.
Yes, I can tell from their faces
but still more handsome than ever
It's up to each person
I don't think so
And the next one is....
All right! Let's see what's his name
Goromaru-san
Goromaru
Athelete Goromaru, Goromaru-san
Yasumura-san
What? Yasumura-san
Goromaru-san, Goromaru-san
next
Goromaru-san
Goromaru-san, Goromaru-san, Goromaru-san
Maeda-san, Goromaru-san
Maeda-san???
I'm sorry
Whyyyy?
It should be Goromaru-san then
Isn't it?
Let's listen the answer from him
Sound director, Goromaru.
It's the name that is easy to remember
but still why can't Katomina remember it
because it is not the trendy name any more so...
It still is!
Don't mess it up! That's not good.
<We got only one question left and NGT is only 1 point ahead
< And the question that will decide this battle is
If you can't remember his name, that will be terrible.
Who?
He is the real producer!
He is the real deal of this channel
And last question is him
I can't remember at all
Who is he???
Who is heee??
Well, he introduced himself as a camera man but
He actually is this programme producer
the real one
He's genuine
If you can't answer his name correctly or make him feel displeased
He can end this programme immediately!
What?? I'm scared!!
To end this programme right now is also possible
It's up to you guys
Do you think that everyone still remembers your name?
I think they all can't remember my existence at all
They will never make it
I see, but do you still want them
to remember your name?
I think so...If anyone can remember mine, I think I'm going to help her in this programme
Honestly
that makes sense
yes
And that name is also his real name.
I didn't hear what he said back there
That changes nothing. He is still our producer.
I've just asked Rikatan here
and she also can't remember his name
And that is already recorded so beware of what will happen
Seriously, next episode you guys may not be able
to be here anymore.
So it's the time to see your answers
Nakamura-san, Nakamura-san
nakata-san
Kobayashi-san
Nakamura-san, Nakamura-san
Fukushima-san
Kanda-san
It's not. It's Samuta-san.
Sorry, Samuta-san
Well, sorry. Samuta-san
Sorry
Next is
Kobayashi-san , Nakamura-san
Yoshimura-san, Takamura-san
Kobayashi-san, Tomita-san
Naoe-san
Yoshimura-san
Still can't tell what the correct one is
It's too various
Yamada-san, Are you ok?
Your face is like that for a while already
It's such a funny face if you see it through the monitor
It's really funny
I'd like to tell that Yamada always call herself
"Tomonaga Mio-san"
Eh? really? I see
It's not! Just kidding! It is.
Other members also say they think the same
I don't think so
- it really is
I don't like it
What do you think, Mio-chan?
I'd like to cry. I don't like it at all.
Let's have both to stand next to each other
Let's see
Are you sure?
Yes
I don't want to...or else everyone will know the truth
What truth?
I'd like to see it
< Then will Tomonaga and Yamada look alike?
Come and stand close to each other
They look alike when they are smiling
yes, they are
yes
It looks like the older sister who has just become a city girl
and the younger sister who still lives in suburb
All right! Let him tell us what his name is
What's your name?
Nice to meet you
Everyone, nice to meet you
NTV Producer
Nakamura
Yeah! I got it!
HKT48 got 4 points
and NGT got 1 point
Are you guys ok?
yes, are you guys really ok?
From my observation it looks like
Otaki often got the correct answer
Yes, I got it all correct!
That's great!
Her appearance may look like that but
she is really a good serious girl
It may look incoherent
I do take it seriously when it's about relationship
so I always observe everyone
And that's all we got today!
The result is
NGT48 got 22 points
HKT48 got 24 points
HKT48 is the winner
And that is our first furious battle!
Katomina-chan, what do you think?
I'm quite annoyed with my own bad memory.
so you're annoyed with yourself
Are you ok?
Where is the luxury cafe?
It's totally different from the picture
<The members will go travelling after this
SashiKita Furious Battle
<Official announcement from the programme
<SashiKita Furious Battle will also be broadcasted via Internet
<You can find it on Hulu and NTV On Demand
<For more information please visit our programme official website
< She who debuted as a part-time AKB but
< after passing tests,
now she got promoted to NGT
<Ogino Yuka
<Nishigata Marina
<Seiji Reina
Sorry to keep you waiting
<Those are serious feelings
which we still do not know
<HKT48 x NGT48 Eating Wanderer girls
Still not there yet? Eh?
Well, I still can't see anywhere that
looks like the place we are going to
Can't find it at all
Are we lost?
wrong way?
but
Don't tell me that..
Wait wait. Look!
Eh? It's old.
so it's different from what you imagined then
yes, totally different
it ruined what I imagined
It should be a luxury cafe, shouldn't it?
but old places always get more delicious foods though.
let's try
ok
Welcome!
ok, let's get in
Excuse me
Sorry to keep you waiting. Here is your curry ramen
oh! here it is
it made me hungrier
looks delicious
but it's quite different from other ramens
it is
it's served with rice
great
Thank you
It looks great
Curry rice is here
Thanks
eh? why does it come with dessert?
Served with dessert is great, isn't it?
Omelet rice is here!
- wow
Shall we eat and talk at the same time?
1 2...Let's eat
let's eat
Delicious
really?
It's not too spicy
let's eat
I'm hungry so it's more delicious
It is so delicious
< Nishigata applied for AKB but
couldn't make it and failed 6 years ago
< And got qualified to be part-time AKB
< when she was 18 years old
< and in the 2nd draft
< she became an official NGT member
< The thing that pushed her into
sadness and disappointment is
Do you remember when we were at our part-time performance
It was only me who got blamed
yes, I do
yes, it really did
The dance instructor was very strict
yes, very strict
you were only the one who got blamed
I see, It's you, Gatapi
That time I felt like being here was not the place for me
I was so stressed out
In the 3rd round of the draft qualification
where I got qualified
but I was not sure which way I should take.
yes
I thought that I will not go on the actual day
yes, it sounded very serious
I told myself that it's not my place
and I shouldn't go
Gatapi!!
That's your story, I've just known
Here is tissue
Thanks, Seiji-chan
You looks terrible
You're older than me. Don't be like this
Do you know that the older, the easier to cry.
I'm just 16 but she is 20 already
< After this CM, we have next episode sample for everyone
When you failed so many times,
did you think to give up on your dream?
I did, I seriously thought that I don't belong to this place
< Please check the full episode of Ogino's sad story on Hulu
< Next episode! Which member will be selected
from the foreigner that they were fake idol!
I love you
I want you I need you
You are the fake one!
<This will be the first time for NGT members to get face slammed in cake